♪你若寻求的是温柔♪
♪If you search for tenderness ♪
♪这并不难求♪
♪It isn't hard to find♪
♪那份爱能支撑你活下去♪
♪You can have the love You need to live♪
♪但你若寻求的是诚实♪
♪But if you look for truthfulness♪
♪不如盲目活着♪
♪You might just as well be blind♪
♪想得到并不容易♪
♪It always seems to be so hard to give♪
♪真诚 多么孤单的词语♪
♪Honesty is such a lonely word♪
♪没有人是真诚的♪
♪Everyone is so untrue♪
好  我觉得行了  很好
Yeah, I think we're good. That's good.
行吗  很好
-Yeah? -Yeah.
好吗   -好  很好啊
-Yeah? -Yeah. I mean, yeah.
挺好的  老兄
Pretty good, man.
有趣的意思  对吗
That means it's funny, right?
我觉得是"好"
I think good.
然后  你要做...
And then you're gonna do the...
你那套东西   -对 对啊
-Your whole, like, thing? -Yeah...
去他的  对吧  燥就完事了
I mean fuckk it, right? Just fucking go nut-nut.
纯过度  巨无聊  怎么样
Pure excess, full bore, yeah?
行
Yeah.
怎么  不好吗
-What? No? -No...Yeah, I think.
没事  我已经能抗得住压力了
No, it's like I've gone anti-fragile.
我...我可以顾及任何事
I can accommodate anything.
如果我开始怀疑自己的话  就崩盘了
If I start second guessing, it collapses.
对  我觉得你说得对
Right. I think that is right.
这他妈啥都有了  肯定会终身难忘的
This is the full fucking thing. It's gonna be epic.
这他妈啥都有了
This is the full fucking thing.
继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 7 集
没问题  对吧  都合理吧
We're good, right? All makes sense?
对  做得不错  小罗
Oh, yeah, this is great work, Rome.
但  显然重点是
Well, obviously, the main thing is
企业文化这类东西
the organizational cultural thing.
我觉得  所有人都认同  收购 Gojo 是很合理的
I think, you know, everyone agrees that GoJo makes sense.
不需要再说服他们了
No one needs persuading of that.
很棒  我现在有点后悔  通宵
Ah, well, kind of regret staying up all night
干这事了
with my assholes then.
不是的  重点是  懂行的我们
No. It's just about, you know us here who get it
起个促进作用[润滑轮胎]确保没有分歧[摩擦过大]
oiling the wheels and making sure there's no friction.
那当然  毕竟我觉得
Well, of course. I mean, I would say
处理与人相关的事  对我们来说问题不大
we could handle the human stuff without too much issue.
这无需我们操心
That needn't concern us
其实  我们之中有人  天生就擅长搞这个
that actually comes naturally to some of us.
所以  我才着墨于
Which is why I focused
业务整合的益处和交易细节
on integration benefits and deal detail.
很好啊  我只是从大局来看
Great. Yeah. I'm just saying, big picture.
大局是由小细节组成的  所以..
Well, big picture is made from small details so...
各位  各位  行了   -商科的基本
Guys, guys, honestly,
紧张作祟而已  你们已经做得很好了
it's just nerves. You've done really great work.
我们去协助你爸谈这笔交易吧
Let's go and help your dad make the deal.
好  好吧
Yeah. All right.
挺会喊话的  勇敢的心[同名战争电影]   -我尽力了
-Nice rally cry, Braveheart. -I try.
你今晚去吗   -肯的盛宴吗
And you're going tonight? -Ken Fest?
是的   -应该不会
-Yeah.  I wouldn't think so.
如果马特森去的话  没准可以去追谈一下
If Matsson does, maybe for follow-up?
会很触目惊心吧
It's gonna be pretty horrific.
看看你哥  在移动厕所里翻滚下坡
Your brother in a...port-a-potty rolling down a hill.
我可能会去  只是为了看看有多糟
I might have to go just to see how bad it is.
真是好兄弟
Brothers.
去你的  我纯粹看戏
Oh, fuck you. It's pure rubbernecking.
好吧  什么情况
Okay? What's this?
可能是马特森来早了
Maybe Matsson's here early?
还是  她[凯莉]要  产下和老爸的孩子了
Or she's gonna give birth to Dad's baby
伴随着我们吟唱撒旦弥撒的歌声
while we chant a Satanic mass?
仿佛他还在经历中年危机都八十岁了
It's like he's having a midlife crisis, aged 80.
没事的   -不  很有事  小罗
It's fine. No, it's not, Rome.
他在操一个比他小五十岁的助理
He's fucking an assistant who's 50 years younger than him.
这不是什么危机  这很正常
It's not a crisis. That's normal.
这恰好与危机相反
It's the opposite of a crisis.
我们都应该感到神他妈的幸运
We should all be so fucking lucky.
大家好   -太好笑了
-Hi-ya. -That's so funny.
好  开香槟呢
-Okay. Champagne? -Yeah.
你们已经谈好了吗
Did you do it already?
当我们不在的时候  你搞定 Gojo 了吗  爸
Did you land GoJo already without us, Dad?
我们不是在庆祝
We're not celebrating.
前途漫漫
Long road ahead.
宽活宜人的路途  清风携过我们的发稍
Lovely long open road. Wind in our hair.
清风拂过你的发稍
Wind in your hair?
我们收到了一个消息
We've had a vibration.
我一直在和一个熟人来往
I've been speaking to a contact
他有司法部的通路   -劳里吗
with connections at DOJ.  Laurie?
我们的朋友很多
Well, we have a number of friends.
非公开的消息表明
And, the word is, on the down-low that
他们已经审完了所有资料
they've seen everything now
也复查过了
they've reviewed,
对于我们的配合程度 他们很满意
and they're happy with how we're engaging
现在 他们认定肯德尔夸大了事实
and they're coming to the view that Kendall over-promised.
或许有些人 当年是有些调皮捣蛋
And perhaps some men were terribly naughty back in the day
但 并不涉及整体 无需制裁
but nothing systemic, nothing sanctioned.
但会有一个数额[罚款]
It's going to be a number.
只是数额吗    -无需监禁
Just a number? Nothing custodial.
任何人都不用   -不用坐牢了吗
For anyone. No prison?
不用  我们觉得不会
Nope, we don't think so.
这杯敬我们   -敬我们
-Here's to us! -To us!
以及...敬正义
And to justice!
敬正义  没错
-To justice. Yeah. -To justice.
我会记得的
I'll remember.
恭喜你  爸  你又成功了
Well, congratulations, Dad. You've done it again.
太好了
It's great.
希望这种事别再发生了  对吧
Let's just hope you don't do it again, right?
吸取教训了
No. Lessons learned.
对了  敬汤姆
And here's to Tom!
前途漫漫  别庆祝得太早了
Long road ahead. No premature celebrations.
没错  我表示赞成
Absolutely. Amen to that!
给我满上  好吗
Top me up, why don't ya?
乡间小路  引我回家[同名歌曲]
Take me home, country roads!
我去下公共男厕
I'm just gonna run to the little boy's room.
好了 好了 不要到处乱晃了
Okay. Enough. No more mooning.
也别再庆祝了 Go Jo! Go Jo! Go Jo!
No more backslapping.
你好啊
Hello.
你好
Hello?
挪过去一点  好兄弟
Hey, scooch over for a little bit, buddy.
谢谢你  格雷格
Thank you, Greg.
太棒了
Yes!
操 操 操 操
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
操  爽爆了
Yeah, fuck yeah!
什么  怎么了
What? What?
发生什么了  你还好吗
What is going on? Are you okay?
抱歉  格雷格  我激动得有点不能自持了
Apologies, Greg, I may have gotten a little carried away.
但我只是过来跟你说
But I just popped around to say
没人要去坐牢了
that no one is going to jail.
格丽和司法部谈过了
Gerri spoke to the DOJ
咱韦斯达二人组..自由了
and the Waystar Two...-are free.
好  确定吗
-Okay. Is it real?
是好消息来着
It was good news.
目前情况如何  比如说
What are we looking at in terms of...
都是什么样的答复
What are the responses looking like?
你的重点邀请名单中  有八成的人会来
I think about 80% of your A list is "yeses"
1.5成的人还不确定
and 15% are "maybes."
好吧  不确定就是不会来了  咱们现实点
Okay. Well, "maybes" are "nos," let's not live in a dream world.
所以  有谁会来
But who's in?
我随便一想都很不错
Off the top of my head, it's great.
迪翁巴里 JP 大卫   -很好
Dion, Barry, JP, David...  -Nice.
安娜 汤姆·托利 杰夫 埃隆 卢卡斯
-...Anna, Tom Tory, Jeff, Elon, Lukas,
詹妮弗和艾玛都会来  克洛伊不确定
Jennifer and Emma, "yeses."  Chloe is still a "maybe."
那..  我兄弟姐妹呢
And... and the sibs?
这个...
Yeah.
好  随便吧  没事
Okay. No. Whatever. Fine.
这很屌了  康福莉  听着
This is fucking cool, Comfry. Hey, hey, listen
你也要玩得开心  好吗  所有人
you have a good time, too, yeah? Like everyone.
服务生  派对  工程师  DJ  团队
Servers, fucking, the imagineers, the DJ crew, you know
一切绝对平等
this is highly egalitarian like
做好你的工作  但也给我他妈的喝起来
do your job, but fucking get your drink on,
尽情享受吧
get your buzz on.
只要你够酷  就没有界限
There's no boundaries if you're cool.
指挥中心完毕  准备引爆全场吧
Mission Control out! Shit is about to pop off.
开趴啦
Party!
今天我过生日  都去他妈的
It's my birthday! fuck You!
我回来啦
Hey.
Go Jo 那边可能会出问题
There might be a problem with GoJo.
好  马特森在哪儿呢
Okay. Where's Matsson?
他就派了些夏尔巴人[小喽喽]  他自己不来了
He's sent Sherpas. He's not coming.
好了
Okay.
结束了  让那些小破孩滚蛋  会不开了
It's off.  Tell these kids to fuck off. Meeting cancelled.
这见他们也没坏处啊  爸
Okay. Well, what's the downside, Dad?
不然的话  可能显得咱们有点任性
You know, meet these guys, could read petulant not to?
是他自己送无名小卒来的
-If he wants to send a nobody...
他的首席财务官和一整个团队都来了.
-Well, his CFO-and a whole team of people...
他是不是要去参加那个狗屁派对
-He's going to this fucking party isn't he?
他上哪去了  做美甲去了吗
Where is he? Getting his nails done,
还是漂菊花去了
asshole whitened?
我感觉我们可能要讨好他
I think we might have to court him
一点点才能成事   -不行 不行
a little is the thing. Nah..Nah..
像这样的开始 是不好的预兆
It's bad fucking juju to start like this.
至少我们可以
Can we not at least...
先跟那些无名小卒谈谈...  -不行还有其他选择
-talk to the nobodies and... -No! -No. We have other options.
我们真有的选吗  这很可能是
-Do we though? This could be
逃脱传统媒体死局的最后一次机会了
our last chance to avoid the legacy media graveyard.
弗兰克已经联系了南  谈皮尔斯的事
Frank's reached out to Nan about Pierce.
什么  认真的吗  又要回头追皮尔斯了吗
What? Seriously? We're going after Pierce again?
多让人激动啊
It's exciting.
好  就这样  所有人给我回去工作
Okay. That's it. Everyone back to work.
这笔交易是很合理  也很有收益
The deal makes sense. It's a great deal
但他谈不下这笔生意  因为他是个傲慢的白痴
but he won't make the deal because he's an arrogant prick.
行  马特森是个混球  他妈的绝对是
Fine. Matsson's an asshole. fucking of course he is.
可是  我们就要这样  把唯一的救生艇扔掉吗
But do we burn our only parachute because of that?
这只是一项明智的商业举措  小西
It's just smart business, Shiv.
我可不想交高价  况且到了最后
I don't wanna pay over the odds. And eventually,
市场会教他做人  让他回来找我交易
the market will make him make the deal.
除非有人先给他们更多好处
Unless someone makes a better offer first.
没错  爸  就是这样  我们的规模有问题
Yeah, Dad, this is it. We have a scale issue.
我们的流媒体平台就是垃圾
Our streaming platform is for shit.
而且  我们没有任何看着有起色的项目
And... we have nothing that looks like growth.
所以  我们必然要转向流媒体
This gets us consequentially into streaming
进入体育博彩 以及社交媒体领域
it gets us into sports betting, it gets us into social media.
转型的窗口就这么点大
We have a little window.
错过了这个 我们就要沦落到
Miss this and we end up being a pilot fish
从贝索斯牙缝里找肉吃的境地了
nibbling leftovers from Bezos's fucking teeth.
凯莉  你说了什么来着  关于马特森的
Kerry? What was it, that thing you said about Matsson?
他觉得自己是个天才
Thinks he's a genius.
不就是创造了一项好技术吗  去他的吧
He's made one good piece of tech. fuck him.
谢谢你的建议  凯莉  但是“去他的吧"
We appreciate your input, Kerry, but "fuck him"
不是什么好计策   -这是个好计策
is not good tactics.  -It is good tactics.
爸  求你了  要是你不想跟马特森谈
Dad, please, if you don't wanna talk to Matsson,
没关系  我去
fine but let me.
或者我也行  我们俩一起
-Or let me. Or we can both do it.
他不是要去参加派对吗
He's gonna be at the party, right?
你们要去吗
You're going?
反正没坏处
Can't hurt.
好吧  但别太强硬了
Fine. But don't go in too strong.
这是个黑箱子  盲人摸象  而且我不想花冤枉钱
This is a black box and I don't want to overpay.
好  知道了  交给我吧
Yeah. Got it. I'm on it.
行  我...重新安排一下时间  我能搞定
Yeah, I'll reorganize my diary. I got it.
既然你要去
Since you're going
就把这个拿给他吧  当面拿给他
you might as well give him this in person.
好  没问题
Oh, yeah. Okay.
你怎么想的  他会喜欢吗
What do you think? Do you think he'll like it?
不是  我只是...感觉太爽了  你明白吗
No, I just... I feel amazing, you know?
我的感官又变灵敏了  空气闻起来都更甜了
My senses are heightened. The air smells sweeter.
我感觉好像我可以既超凡脱俗
And, you know, it's like I can see the poetry
又享受人间烟火
and all little mundane things.
这...我
It's...
我一定要玩儿疯
I'm gonna get so fucked up.
这样可以吗
Okay. Is that okay?
当然  你不用征求我的同意
-Yeah, you don't need my permission. -Okay.
但  你要玩多疯
Like, how fucked up?
你们好   -你们好
-Hi there. -Hi there.
我  汤姆·威姆士丹
Tom Wambsgans!
不用坐牢啦
Not going to prison!
你好   -我们需要所有人
Hi. We're asking everyone
把外套和手机交给我们保管
to hand in their coats and phones.
肯德尔希望 大家把关注当下 作为送给他的礼物
Kendall would like his present to be everyone being present.
好啊  去他的吧  我才不要呢
-Yeah. fuck off. I'm not doing that.
对  除非你拿电击枪  把我们打昏
-Yeah, you're gonna have to tase us.
-你的外套  -不必了
And your coat?
外套我要穿着  我有权穿外套  多谢了
I will remain coated. Thank you as is my right.
说说看  发生什么事了
So come on. What? What happened?
农场那些事
Ranch stuff.
啥  有匹马不让你操  还是怎么回事
What, a horse didn't want you to fuck it? What?
他跌了个跟头 别说什么“跌跟头"
-He had a fall. -Don't say "had a fall"
听着  像是我已经89岁了似的  不是
that sounds like I'm 89. No!
我和马克西姆拿到了民调结果
Maxim and I actually got some polling results
我们一起喝了点白兰地
we shared a Cognac
高兴地跳起了爱尔兰吉格舞  然后我滑倒了
and then I slipped doing a little Irish jig.
行吧  农场那点事
Oh, okay. Ranch stuff.
是啊   -懂了  你是真牛仔
Got it. A real cowboy.
我的天  这也太有肯德尔那味了
Oh, my God. This feels disgustingly Kendall.
小塔去哪了  她在忙吗   -是的
So where's Tabs? She busy? Yeah.
又来  你杀了她吗   -是的
Again? Or did you kill her?
进展非常顺利  我来告诉你吧
It's going great, I'll have you know.
她这人有点无聊  就是这样
It's just a bit boring is all. That's all I'm saying.
行吧  你们的性生活和谐
Okay. The relationship was fine sexually
你也享受这种亲密感之类的吗
and you're loving the intimacy and all?
对  我享受这种亲密感
Yes.  I love the intimacy.
我喜欢别人真正地了解我
I love people really getting to know me.
好吧
Yeah.
说得好像 你是香饽饽似的
Like you're the fucking catch of the day.
你比我还一塌糊涂
You're more fucked up than I am.
恭喜各位
Congratulations!
你们刚刚在肯德尔·罗伊的世界出生了
You've just been born into the world of Kendall Roy!
好吧  沉浸式剧场
Okay. Immersive theater.
虽然  可以邀请我做顾问的  算了  随便吧
I mean, I could have consulted, but whatever.
神啊
Oh, Jesus.
如果我们刚被生出来  那么..
So if we've just been born then...
好的  所以我现在就是在
Okay. So I'm inserting myself
把我自己塞进我妈的阴道吗
into my mom's vagina now?
是这样吗
-Wow. -Is that what's happening?
冷漠又厌客 应该是她的
Cold and inhospitable, seems to check out.
我正在反复进入我母亲的身体
I am repeatedly entering my own mother.
是不是...不对
Is that... That's not right.
这是我妈的小妹妹  你们懂的
This is my mom's cooch, so you know.
你是在暗示她下面很松  你可能需要..
And you're implying that it's massive so you might wanna
把我妈的阴道收紧一点
tighten my mother's vagina.
你好哇  我汤姆·威姆士丹  自由人  你怎么样
Hey, Tom Wambsgans, free man, how's it going?
我  格雷戈里·赫施  不进监狱了
Gregory Hirsch, not going to prison.
很高兴见到你
Pleased to meet you!
看看你油头粉面的  你个滑头鬼
Look at you all gussied up, you slick little fuck.
谢谢你的夸奖   -真不错
-Well, thank you. -It looks nice.
感觉不错 真的
Yes. I'm feeling good.
就是 你有没有见到过 康福莉
Yeah. Say have you seen, Comfry?
肯的公关  头发老是有点
Ken's PR with the hair always kind of
乱糟糟的...  -格雷戈里·约翰·赫施
in a messy... Gregory John Hirsch,
你有心上人了吗
you got a crush?
我的天哪   -怎么了
-Oh, my God. -What?
她看着人很不错啊
She seems like a nice person.
你跟她远不是一个档次的人  朋友
Well, I mean, she's way out of your league, man.
就好像稻草人鬼 约杰奎琳·奥纳西斯[第一夫人] 出来一样
I mean, it's like a haunted scarecrow asking out Jackie Onassis.
完全是自杀式任务
-It's a suicide mission.
啊 对对对 我懂了 汤姆
Really. -Oh, yeah. -Sure... Tom.
不不不 我不是在讽你
-No...This is not a razz.
格雷格  她是女神
Greg, she's a goddess and you're a...
你就是个...两米高的克鲁马努人[晚期智人]
you're a nine-foot Cro-Magnon man.
你根本都不该妄想约她出来
I mean, you shouldn't even be really thinking about her.
你这样会让她很尴尬
You're gonna put her in a tough spot.
你听我说  我并不是不知道  我和她之间
Look, I'm not unaware of the discrepancy
生理条件上的差异   -那天壤之别
in terms of our physical circumstances. It's a chasm.
我有个初步的搭汕想法  那就是..
Well, I have an initial approach which is...
你像一本诱人的书
"You're like a fascinating book
我渴望翻开阅读
I'd like to crack open."
好吧  那 那 你是怎么追到小西的
Okay. Well, how'd... How'd you get Shiv?
她跟你也不是一个档次的啊
She's out of your league.
你很狂啊 格雷格   -怎么样
Oh! Testy, Greg! -Well?
好啊  格雷格  我告诉你  我的老二有红杉树那么大
-Well, Greg, I'll tell you. I got a dick the size of a Red Sequoia
我做起爱来  就像高速列车  懂了吗  满意了吧
and I fuck like a bullet train. Okay? Satisfied?
证明一下,   -什么
Prove it.  What?
好了  那么  马特森在哪儿
Okay, so where's Matsson?
可能站在某个角落
He's probably standing in a corner somewhere
用手表监测自己的生物特征数据吧
monitoring his biometrics from his watch.
我们要不要简单地跟肯打声招呼
Should we just say hi to Ken really fast?
意思意思   -好啊
-Just to get out of the way? -Yeah.
你好  贝里
-Oh, hey, hey, Berry.
你好   -肯在哪儿
-Hi. -Where's Ken?
贵宾室
-VIP.
好
Okay.
今天很有标志性的意义
Today is pretty fucking iconic.
是啊
Yeah.
等一下
Wait a second.
谁..谁让你们进来的
Who... let you guys in?
只有朋友才可以入场   -那不就没人了吗
This is friends only. Shouldn't it be empty then?
比我快了一步
Beat me by one second.
生日快乐  老男人
Happy birthday, old man.
我只是想说  我来这里  只是因为
Just to say, I'm only here because
我听说这将是一场五维灾难
I heard this was going to be a five-dimensional catastrophe
我想看你粉身碎骨
and I want to watch you crash and burn.
过来   -好吧  抱一个
-Come here. -Oh. Yeah, all right. Hugsy.
伙计  感觉你老了
Man, it's like you fueled.
你确定你只有四十岁吗  你看起来糟透了
Are you sure you're only 40? You look like shit.
怎么  没有贺卡吗  我很失望
What? No card? I'm disappointed
因为  你通常都会给我写点  感人词句的
because you normally write me such lovely letters.
是的  没有写  我找不到一张既写着“生日快乐"
Oh, yeah. No, I couldn't find one that said
又写看“早日康复“的贺卡
both "Happy Birthday" and "Get Well Soon".
好吧...  很高兴你们能来
Well, I'm glad you came.
意义非凡   -是啊  毕竟开车只要十分钟
It says a lot. Yeah, it was a ten-minute drive.
这样啊
Uh...
好了  在你哭之前  给我个拥抱吧
Okay. Well, give me a hug before you start weeping.
见到你很高兴
It's good to see you.
你好  小肯   -我勒个擦
-Hi, Kenny. -Holy shit.
我勒个擦  大军到齐了   -是啊
Holy shit. Gang's all here?
生日快乐   -谢谢  伙计  怎么...
-Yeah. -Happy birthday. Thank you. Hey, man, what...
怎么回事...  发生了什么事
what's this? What happened?
对政治上的突破  有点兴奋过头了  所以..
Well, a little overexcited about a political breakthrough, so...
好吧   -是啊
-Okay. -Yeah.
但是...怎么还穿着外套? 你要走吗  还是...
But what... what's with the coat? You're not staying or...
外套而已  我想穿着
It's a coat. I like it.
那么  你们觉得怎么样
So, what do you think?
很酷  我能问问你吗
It's cool. Can I ask you
你用妈妈的跨部前
did you ask for Mommy's permission
有没有征得她的同意
for the use of her squatch?
什么  从版权的角度来说吗
What? From a copyright perspective?
只是.. 算我老士吧
Well, it's just, you know, call me old-fashioned
但我觉得你在建造别人阴道的
but I think you should ask before you construct
巨型复制品之前  应该先问一下的  不是吗
a giant replica of someone's vagina. No?
罗曼  放轻松  是的  你可以把它带回家
Roman, relax. Yes, you can take it home with you.
好吧  那么  继续吧  告诉我们都有谁来了
Okay. So. Go on, tell us. Who's here?
有谁没来   -你爸
Who isn't? -Your dad.
你妈   -你的妻子和孩子
-Your mom. -Your wife and kids.
所有真正的朋友
-Any real friends.
还有生意伙伴  斯图伊  在吗
I mean business folks, yeah. Stewy?
说真的  我们可以和他友好来往一下
I mean, honestly, we could do with building some bridges.
劳伦斯·易在吗  卢卡斯·马特森呢
So, yeah, Lawrence Yee? Lukas Matsson?
是的  他们都在  在某处
Yeah. They're all here. Somewhere.
我有东西给你们  看这边  走这边  走
Hey, I got something to show you. -This way.
很好   -走了小威
-Great. -Hey, Will.
好   -你好 内
Hey, Nate. -Yeah.
内 我.. 我要带他们四处看看
Nate, I'm gonna show these guys around.
事实上  我这儿有爸给你准备的礼物
Hey, I actually got something from Dad,
也算有我一份吧
and myself, I suppose.
这是什么
-What is it?
是你的乳牙和苹果礼品卡
-Oh, it's...it's your baby teeth and an iTunes gift card.
很好的  不.. 反正是个好东西
It's nice. No, it's a... it's a nice thing.
我们...我们希望你会喜欢
We hope you'll like it.
好了  我给你们看点好东西   -好
Okay. Let me show you some shit. Okay.
所以 我咨询了格拉德威尔[记者] 和 赫拉利[历史学家]
So I consulted with Gladwell and Harari
还有洛夫洛克[环境学家] 和爆米花 这里的这个东西
and Lovelock and Popcorn and this in here
非常专业
it's pretty technical
但  这是我们在能力范围内做出的
but this is the best we could come up with
对社会发展方向的最优规划
on the likely directions of society
因此  会有点枯燥  但是...
so a little dry, but...
在肃清站街女行动中
汤姆·威姆士丹之妻被捕  汤姆蒙羞
无能兄弟 于悲惨的
打飞机意外事件中死去
我认为 很准确  准确 -总统
...accurate, I would say. Accurate. -President.
韦斯达董事长 肯德尔·罗伊
当选世界联邦政府的总统
这样死了也不赖
Not a bad way to go.
而且  这里的人现在都在脑补我打飞机了
Also, we got people in here picturing me jerking off
无能兄弟 于悲惨的
打飞机意外事件中死去
那么  谁才是真正的赢家呢
so who's the real winner?
天啊
Oh, man.
康纳·罗伊当选总统
[拉裤兜联盟的总统]
如果麦卡特尼用这个发推特怎么办
What if, McCartney tweets this?
这不是..我是说  开开玩笑  不要紧..
This is not... I mean, jokes are all very well and...
但是  拜托伙计  我在紧要关头
Come on, man, I'm breaking through.
肯  我不确定你是否知道  但老康的支持率
Ken, I'm not sure that you're aware but Conn is
接近百分之一  所以...  -百分之一？
pulling very close to 1% so...-1%?
真的吗    -恭喜
Congrats. -Really?
那也有四百万人
That's four million people
足以影响竞选结果
and it's enough to sway the race.
我很想看看  谁会先来巴结我
And I am interested to see who comes crawling first
是默克尔先来求我 拯救民主政府
Merkel, begging for me to save democracy
还是索罗斯[金融大亨] 在树上给我唱小夜曲
or Soros serenading me from the trees.
有一说一  你确实拉过裤兜
You did, however, actually shit your bag.
是的  你知道为什么吗  因为我带你们这两个混蛋
Yeah, you know why? Because I took you two fucking assholes
去露营  因为咱爸根本不屑去
on a camping trip because Dad couldn't be bothered.
这就是原因,   -好了  好了  好了
That's why!  -Okay...
然后我吃了不新鲜的鱼   -好了 好了 好了
-And I ate some bad fucking fish. -Okay...
好了 好了 好了   -—派胡言
Hey.  -This is bullshit!
不好意思  我们能不能... 我们能把
Excuse me, hey, can we... can we take down
菜袋子康纳的那幅 拿下来吗
the crap sack Connor piece, please?
老康 老康 老康
Conn?
拿下来了  只是开个玩笑  好吗
It's coming down. It's a joke, okay?
拜托伙计  放轻松   -我很好
-Come on, man. Loosen up. -I'm good.
好了 好了 好了   -把外套脱了吧
-Okay. -Loose the coat. Yeah.
好了
Okay.
好了  我要去招待客人了  晚点再聊
All right, I gotta circulate. We can check in later.
好  那太好了  我很乐意
-Yeah... That would be great. -You know, I'd like that.
今晚很美好  我很高兴你们能来
It's a great night. I'm happy you're here.
史上最棒的生日
fucking best birthday ever.
好了  回见
Okay. Later.
生日快乐
套现
然后滚蛋
股份收购提案
你好  你好哇
Hey...
你好  听说树屋那边好像排起了队
Hey. Oh, I think there's a line at the treehouse
你能去处理一下吗  谢谢
actually, can you fix, please? Thank you.
你好吗   -你好  很高兴遇到你
-What's up? -Hey. I'm glad I ran into you.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me too.
因为  我可能要向媒体通报  对你不利的情况
Right, because I might have to brief the press against you.
..所有媒体吗
Oh. The... the whole press?
是的  肯德尔真的火力全开了
Yeah. Just Kendall's really going balls-to-the-wall
而你  属于敌对阵营
and, you know, you're on the other team.
但我会尽量报道得有针对性  留点余地
But I'm gonna try to keep it targeted rather than terminal.
诚挚感谢  女士
Thank you kindly, ma'am.
你...你真好
That's very kind of you.
我该..  我该怎么报答你呢
How can I possibly repay you?
康福莉   -能这样做...
-Hey, Comf. -You are a very fair maiden for...
你真是个公正的姑娘
for such activities, for such a kind...
非常公正无私的姑娘
a very evenhanded maiden.
你没事吧
You good?
没事 没事
Yeah.
是的  所以...爸送了我生日礼物
Yeah. So...Dad sent me something for my birthday.
是吗
Okay?
对我持续不断地精神蹂躏
It's a little Trojan mind fuck.
他想把虫塞进苹果糖里
He's trying to slip a maggot in the candy apple.
他提出  要买下我在公司的全部股份
He's offering to buy me out of my share in the company.
好吧 哇哦 那是多少...
Okay. Wow. Like what is that?
多少金额
In terms of a number?
二十亿  但这是一场心理战  他只是
Two bill. But, it's a mind game. He's just...
担心我不会继续对他手下留情了
he's worried I'm not gonna let him keep on living rent free up here.
所以呢   -去他的
-And? -And fuck him.
对吧  可能我会拒绝参与
Right? Maybe I refuse to engage.
这还他妈 怎么玩心理战
Mind game that, motherfucker.
行  是很棒  但是..
Yeah. That's great. But...
可能你会接受
maybe you do take it.
可能吧  我也不知道  可能..
Maybe, I don't know. Yeah, maybe...
可能我会给你
maybe I buy you
买一颗 丽思卡尔顿[酒店] 那么大的钻石
a diamond the size of the Ritz-Carlton
和一些显赫的报纸
and a few illustrious newspapers.
环球邮报  洛杉矶时报
The Globe and Mail, the LA Times
然后  一整年都在每天的头版头条
I print a front page of
刊登我爸给狗口交的新闻
my dad eating dog dick every day for a year.
然后  我们住在马拉喀什[摩洛哥]  然后操你
And we're living in Marrakesh and I'm fucking you
抽点大麻  然后学习做泥塑
and smoking hash and learning how to turn a lathe?
都挺好
All good.
但我们知道卢卡斯·马特森现在在哪吗
But do we know where Lukas Matsson is right now?
小西和罗曼一直在问员工 马特森的位置
Shiv and Roman have been asking staff for Matsson's location
还在悄悄打听 开私人会议的地方
and inquiring discreetly about a private meeting space.
这样没事吗
Is that okay?
知道了
Okay.
好吧  能让派对团队
Okay. Can the party team
找到马特森  然后请他来树屋找我吗
get eyes on Matsson and ask him to meet me in the treehouse?
好的
Sure.
你能找到卢卡斯·马特森然后说...
Can you find Lukas Matsson and tell...
我问到了
Hey, I have a location.
棒极了  走  -对
-Oh, great. Let's go! -Yeah.
但不要搞砸好吗   -得了吧
-But don't fuck this, yeah? -Oh, come on.
放松点  真的   -请  我们去哪
-Easy. No. -Please, where are we going?
楼上
Upstairs.
什么鬼   -是啊
What the fuck?  -Yeah. I don't know.
我觉得  一个重建了自己童年树屋
I think a 40-year-old man who rebuilds
的四十岁老男人  应该立刻
his childhood treehouse should immediately
登记在性犯罪者名单上
go on the sex offender registry.
你好
Hey.
你们是允许我进去  还是怎么样
Are you letting me in or what's the deal?
你有彩虹带吗  有  我是...
-Do you have a rainbow band? -Yes, I'm... I'm...
我是行走的彩虹带
I'm a walking rainbow band.
他来了   -你们好啊
There he is.  -Oh, hey.
你好   -好吧
-Hey.  Okay.
这家伙不让我们进去
-This guy's not letting us in.
你们在楼下玩好了吗,   -是的  我们玩够了
-You done downstairs? Yeah. We are done.
肯  我们能进入你饱受精神困扰的心房吗
Hey, Ken may we please step inside your mental disorder?
挺好笑   -谢谢
-Good one. -Thanks.
所以呢   -对不起
-Okay. -Sorry. -So?
什么   -没可能的
What? -That's not possible.
好  为什么
Okay. Why?
因为  问题是
Yeah, well, because the thing is
树屋很酷  而你不酷
the treehouse is cool and you're not cool.
对  哦  我好久没见过
Oh, wow, yes. The coolest grown-man's treehouse
这么酷炫的成年人的树屋了
I've seen in quite a while.
好了  好了
Okay. Okay.
不  伙计们  来这边说..
No, seriously, guys, just come over...
过来一下  我们到这来
come over here for a second. -Okay. -Let's go over here.
就一下
Just one second.
对不起  但不开玩笑了.
Sorry, but, like, so joking aside...
好玩笑
Great jokes.
这里真的有正事..
There is actually a real issue here
好吧   -...而我需要小心
and I need to be discreet
因为周围有很多名人
because there's a lot of celebrities around
如果你们进了树屋  就有点
and if you guys were in the treehouse it kinda...
它就有点不像树屋了  懂吧
kinda wouldn't feel like the treehouse, you know?
你是个纳粹爱好者
You're a Nazi lover.
你也是个纳粹爱好者
And you're a Nazi lover.
而我  是自由民主的捍卫者
And I'm a defender of liberal democracy.
好吧   -而这里是
-Okay. -And this here
由乔治·华盛顿的樱桃树建成的  所以..
is made from George Washington's cherry tree, so...
什么玩意
The fuck?
你真的不打算 让我们进去吗
Are you actually not gonna let us in?
还是 就要在 让我们进去之前
Or are you just gonna bullshit us a little bit
糊弄我们一会   -让你们见马特森吗
before you let us in?  -To see Matsson?
这就是你们来的原因  想要促成一个交易
That's why you're here. You're trying to push a deal here.
所以呢   -谁又在乎呢
-So? -Who fucking gives a shit?
有什么区别吗  我只是想跟他聊聊
Like what's the difference? I just wanna talk to him.
高质量"个人行为"
High-quality personal conduct.
你们确实一流
Really top rank.
有什么区别  我想跟他谈谈  那又怎样
What's the difference? I wanna talk to him. So what?
对  你知道  如果我们跟他谈了  会怎样吗
Yeah. And you know what happens if we do talk to him
要么  我们出局  颗粒无收
either we strike out and nothing.
要么  我们成功  韦斯达获利  然后你的资产飙升
Or we succeed, Waystar benefits and your net worth goes up
狂赚几亿美元  -不用谢
-by several hundred million dollars. -You're welcome.
没错   -对
-Right. -Yeah.
可我必须要与"失败者勿入“的情况
But I have to weigh that against the consideration
权衡考虑一下
that "no losers are allowed."
我的老天啊   -好吧  我要进去  这太他妈愚蠢了
Okay. I'm going in. It's fine. This is stupid.
-老弟 老弟    -这很
-This is dumb. -Hey, hey,
看看他  我的天
look at him! -Hey... -Oh, my God.
看到了吗  我被平移了  好吧
Did you see that? I just got moved. -All right.
我的老天  老哥   -不不不
Oh, my God, bro! no...no...
什么  这算什么   -老弟 老弟 冷静
-What? What is this?  -Bro, bro. Calm down.
你真打算阻止我吗
Are you actually gonna... What...stop me?
你真的要因为树屋生气吗   -是的
You're getting worked up ...about a treehouse?  -Yeah.
你知道这有多荒唐吗
-You know how ridiculous that is?
请进  给他手环
-Hey, come on in. Wristband him.
对  给这哥们手环  他叫什么名字
Yeah, wristband this guy. What's his name?
他叫什么名字  他是谁   -不知道
What is his name? Who is he? -No idea.
好  很好  很好   -看到这两位了吗
-Good. So good. -See these two?
别让他俩进去  好吗
-Don't let these two in, okay?
行   -这是我的树屋
-Yeah. -This is my treehouse.
你们不应该靠近这里
You shouldn't be anywhere near here!
发生什么了
-What is happening?
对了  谢谢那个提议  小罗
-Hey, thanks for the offer, Rome.
非常棒  你和老爸很会搞人心态  谢了
Really cool. Great head-fuck from you and Dad, thanks.
难以置信  难以置信
Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
他在说什么  什么提议
What's he talking about? What offer?
天啊  没什么事
Oh, God. That's nothing.
什么事   -没什...只是...只是..
What is it? It's... No, it's a
是迫使他离开控股公司的一个小行动
it's a little move to ease him out of the holding company.
你和爸吗
You and Dad?
他只能卖给家人  对吧
Well, he can only sell to family, right
是的  我想爸把我的名字写上去了
and, yeah, I think Dad put my name on there.
只是家务采购   -是"我想"吗
It's housekeeping.  Oh, I think?
就是纸上的一个名字  小西
It's a name on a piece of paper, Shiv.
什么都不是   -好的
-It's nothing. -Okay.
那我能是纸上的一个名字吗
So can I be the name on the piece of paper?
我拿它甚至都没用  就是抢椅子游戏
I can't even do anything with it, it's musical chairs.
不好意思  只是以往来看
I'm sorry. Just, historically,
谁他妈拥有这家公司是有意义的
who owns the fucking company has been of some interest?
爸和我搞定了
Dad and I handled it.
干嘛  你是想搞懂财务吗
What, you wanna figure out the financing?
“爸和我搞定了”   -对
-"Dad and I handled it"? -So... Yeah.
真机灵啊  行  我很喜欢  很棒
Wow. Oh, that's cute. Yeah, I love that. It's great.
真他妈的棒  操你丫的  我不干了
it's just fucking great. fuck you. fuck this.
他来了
There he is.
卢卡斯·马特森
Lukas Matsson.
编码界的主神奥丁
The Odin of coding.
我的伙计 我的神话 我的巨人
My man, my myth, my fucking monolith.
怎么样啊 兄弟
-What's up, bro? -How are you?
你好啊! 你玩得开心吗
You having a good time?
我看着像是玩得开心吗
Do I look like I'm having a good time?
不  你看着不像   -我不开心
-No, you do not. -I am not.
还是不增长社交吗
Still haven't figured out the socials, huh?
老兄  你应该让你的算法专家帮你修改代码
Dude, you should get your Algo Guy to fix your code.
给你点提醒
Listen, heads up,
我的兄弟伙现在在找你
my siblings, they're looking for you now.
那么 也许我需要找个更私密的地方
Well, maybe I need to find an even more exclusive area then
像是爬行空间之类的地方
-like a crawl space or something.
对  也许吧   -行
-Yeah. Maybe.
他们就像是老一代大公爵的使者
They're like emissaries from the Grand Old Duke of Old.
老爸想收购你  所以他派身边的随从来游说
Dad wants to buy you so he sent his winged dildos to schmooze.
我什么都不能说
I shouldn't say anything.
甚至连我脸上的表情都是商业机密
Even the look on my face is commercially sensitive.
但是  完全不合理对吧
But it makes no sense, correct?
美国铁路公司居然收购了特斯拉
Amtrak buys Tesla.
毕竟依我看  你应该收购了他
I mean, if anything, you should buy him.
你这么认为吗
You think?
我真的很欣赏你中立的解读
Well, I really appreciate your impartial read.
什么事   -拉瓦想打个招呼
-Yeah. -Rava wants to say hi.
没问题
Sure.
但不是现在  等我有空的时候
-Not right now. When I'm ready.
好的
-Okay.
听着  你应该留在这上面  好吗
Listen, you should stay up here, okay?
这样你才不会被强行建立工作关系
So you don't get networked to fuck.
你需要什么吗  我能为你做什么
You need anything? What can I get you?
隐私  女人的性器官  意大利面
Privacy, pussy, pasta.
没问题里斯  可以帮你  女人的性器官啊  可卡因啊  腕表啊
Done. Reece can help you out. Like pussy, coke, wristwatches,
意大利通心粉  都有  他就像是个独立的暗网
fucking garganelli he's like a one-man dark web.
里斯  给你的糖果屋找的顾客  伙计
Yo, Reece, Reece, customer for your candy store, man.
他不是个好人  好好玩
He's not a good guy. Enjoy.
好  谢了
Yeah, thanks.
你好啊,   -来了  他们说你在找我
Hey. they said you were looking for me?
是的  生日快乐   -谢谢
-Hey. Yeah. Happy birthday. -Thank you.
我...我只是想趁...你知道的
I...I just wanted to say hi before, you know,
所有人喝嗨了之前 打个招呼
everyone's too high.
好吧
Right.
我们...我们可能很快就走了  所以..
We... we, might go soon, so...
你不能走  不能  我正在...
Well, you can't go. No, no. I'm doing
我正要上演好戏   -是吗
a whole thing.
我们找了小武当帮来表演
And we got the Tiny Wu Tang Clan.
我们找了一些翻唱武当帮的小伙
These kids we found that do Wu Tang covers.
这...会比听起来的要好  相信我
It's better than it sounds. Trust me.
好吧  -怎么  你玩的不开心吗
Okay. What? Are you not enjoying it?
开心  只是... 人太多了  真是个盛大的派对
Yeah. No, it's a lot of people. It's huge.
真是不留情面  那你的生日派对会做什么
Wow. Savage. What you gonna do for yours?
就只请萨拉和奥尔拉再吃些..白汁意大利面吗
Just Sarah and Orla and some... some pasta alfredo?
兴致上来的话  喝上三杯沙布利白葡萄酒
Three glasses of Chablis if you're feeling naughty
然后11 点就熄灯
and lights out by 11?
事实上  这听起来很不错
That actually sounds really nice to me.
好吧
-Right.
不过听我说  加里...你认识加里吗
-But, listen Gary, you know Gary.
是的  我认识..我认识加里
-Yeah. I know Gary. -Okay.
好吧   -很会摆姿势的小玩偶
Nice little poseable action figure.
他有生殖器吗   -有的有的
Does he have any genitals? -Oh, yes, yes.
有啊   -他有
He does. -Yes.
加里已经先走了
Gary has an early start, so...
好吧 加里一定没见过大场面
Okay. Gary's gotta be fresh for the big meet.
好吧  谢谢  生日快乐
Okay. Thank you. Happy birthday.
对了 你有没有...有没有收到孩子们的礼物
Did you get the kids' present?
他们..他们做了个东西送给你
They've... they've made something for you.
什么  没有  他们给我做了个东西?
-What? No. -Yeah. -They made me something? -Yeah.
不 我没收到   什么时候
No, I didn't... that didn't get to me. What... when?
你到的时候   你..你把它给了谁
When you arrived? -Who did you give it to?
我们...我不知道
-We... yeah. We... I don't know.
我们把它给了某个工作人员
We left it with one of the people.
他们说了会带给你  但是..
They said they would give it to you, but...
-好吧  没关系  我...我会找到的
-Fine. Okay. No, I'll find it. -Yeah.
我会找到的  因为礼物会被登记
I'm gonna find it because it'll be logged.
它...它长什么样
What did it... what did it look like?
就像...就像是个礼物
Like a present.
有...有兔子图案的包装纸
-It had... -Like a present... It had rabbit wrapping paper.
好的  我知道了
All right. Got it.
好吧..
Fine.
谢谢你能来   -没事
Thanks for coming.  Yeah.
知道吗  我可能终于要离开公司了
You know, I might be getting out from the firm, finally.
所以  我们...我们到时候再详谈
So we'll... we should... we'll talk more.
这很好  真的  因为或许这样他们就不用再
It's great, actually, because maybe, you know they'll stop
派打手去公园
sending their goons to the park
然后问保姆
to talk to the nanny about
你多久对孩子们发一次脾气了
how often you lose your temper with the kids.
对不起   这..这显然是不对的
Sorry. Obviously, that's not cool.
我会...我会处理的  我很抱歉
I'll handle it. -I'm sorry.
我...我很抱歉  我并不想.
-I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
在你生日上说这些
-on your birthday.
你不想戳破我生日的泡沫
-You wanna burst my...-burst my birthday bubble?
是的   -好吧  干得“漂亮
-I didn't.  -Well, good job.
好吧  -好吧  兔子  兔子图案的包装纸
-Okay. Okay. Rabbits, rabbit paper.
兔子的   -知道了
-Rabbits. -Got it.
替我向凯文问好
Give my love to Kevin.
加里
Gary.
我为什么没收到那个礼物  我们能找到它吗  拜托
Why didn't that get to me? Can we trace that gift, please?
这是首要任务,   -好的  没问题
-Priority one. -Yes. Absolutely.
哎哟  鞋不错  伙计  用来矫正的吗
Hey, cool shoes, man. Orthopedics?
正厅播放的是我看过的歌单吗
Are they playing from the approved playlist in the main room?
因为我...我要的是一直放节奏感很强的音乐
Because my... my thing was all bangers all the time.
对吗  一直放节奏感很强的歌
Yeah? All bangers all the time.
我想是的   -对吧
-I think so. -Yeah?
马上快放完了  我们去审核一下歌单
They're stopping. Let's read the playlist.
听着  这没什么  没什么..
Listen, this is nothing. It's nothing
但我们...我们能让康纳把外套脱了吗
but can we get Connor to lose his coat?
可以,   -没什么大不了的
-Sure. -Yeah, it's nothing.
他...他在破坏气氛
He's souring the vibe.
他让所有人都觉得冷   不冷吧
And he's making everyone feel cold. -It's not cold, is it?
不  温度正好
-No. It's at a good level.
没错  所以去让他把外套脱了吧  只要他没意见的话
Exactly. So let's encourage him to remove his coat if he wants,
放松点
loosen this thing up.
你们瞧  只是...
Look, it just...
只是这像是一个混蛋的生日派对
it just feels like an asshole's birthday party.
我们第一次开会  我的要求就是
And my thing from the very first meeting
不要让它看起来像是一个混蛋的派对
was that it shouldn't feel like an asshole's birthday party.
懂吧
Yeah.
你好哇   肯   -你好  格雷格  告密的贱人
-Hey, Ken. -Hey, Greg! The snitch bitch.
你..好吧...我喝得够多了
You're... yeah. Well... I've had too much.
我能...我能和你聊两句吗
Can I have one moment with you?
我要去表演了  所以...
I'm about to do my set, so...
好的  我们边走边说吧  我..
Oh, yeah. Yeah, let's ride.
我在想一件事  因为...
Yeah, I was wondering about something because,
我打算约康福莉出来
I was just about to ask Comfry out
然后她说了这事  有点让人担心
and then she said this slightly worrying thing about
有关... 她可能要开记者会
how she might have to do, like, a press brief.
你要和康福莉约会   我的员工康福莉吗
You were gonna ask Comfry out? Comfry, my employee Comfry?
是的  但这事是真的吗
Yeah. But is that right?
我是说  你们..你们要针对我吗
I mean...are you... Do you have to spin against me?
因为  我觉得事情有点
Because I feel like things are kind of slowing down
缓和下来了  对吗
in that regard, right?
没有  再说  你也配不上她  兄弟
No. And she's out of your league, bro.
我...我不这么觉得
Well, yeah, I... I don't see it that way.
我要是约她出去呢
What if I wanna ask her out?
这不合适  但是不行
Inappropriate. But no.
你最好别约她  好吗
It's best you don't, okay?
太复杂了  她在我手下工作
Too complicated. She works for me.
划清界限 政教分离 好吗
Clean lines. Church and State, okay?
好吧  我是说  这不...我认为这并不重要
Okay. I mean, it doesn't...I don't think it really matters
因为事情...   -我说了不行  格雷格
because... -things are... -Well, I said no, Greg.
你说什么 我说了不行
-Sorry. -I said no.
上帝啊  天哪  兄弟
Jesus, dude.  Duh?
你他妈的就像世上最大的寄生虫
You're like the world's biggest fucking parasite.
你就是人形绦虫
You're a human tapeworm.
你还是别再吸你自家的血了
Maybe stop feeding on your own fucking family
换个地方吸吧  好吗
and try sucking some blood elsewhere. Yeah?
你笑什么
What?
我开玩笑的   -好吧
I'm kidding.  Okay.
我是吗   -我..
Or am I? I have...
你在逗我吗  我
Are you kidding? I...
我没在开玩笑  还是我在开玩笑
I'm not kidding. Am I or am I?
你好啊
What's up?
你真他妈混蛋啊  伙计
fucking asshole, man.
快看  他们脸色啊  太阴沉了
Look at their faces. So fucking dour.
这是个庆祝会
It's a festivity,
大家应该高兴点
people are supposed to be festive.
真是扯淡
It's fucking bullshit.
罗曼和爸爸都处在有利位置
Roman and Dad necking in the catbird seat.
你之前知道这次收购的事吗
Did you know anything about this buyout thing?
为什么大家都不开心  这...这是什么
Why is no one happy? What... what is this?
宝贝  你在扫自己的兴  冷静下来吧
Babe, you're harshing your own mellow, just calm down.
我得说  那套绳索真结实
I mean, that is... some substantial rigging.
你说  那得多少钱   -我不知道宝贝
What do you think that cost? I don't know, baby.
你好  康纳  我给你免费赠送
Hi, Connor. I'd like to offer you a
一件羊绒毛衣
complimentary cashmere sweater.
专门送给贵客的
We're handing them out to prestige guests.
不用了 我有外套
I have my coat. I'm fine.
存衣处该收走你的外套的
Well, the coat check was supposed to take that,
但我很乐意代劳
but I'd be happy to.
无意冒犯  我不信任存衣处
Respectfully, I don't trust those things.
我在温哥华一家融合餐厅丢了件挪威的羊毛外套
I lost a Norwegian Wool in a fusion restaurant in Vancouver.
你如果愿意收下这件毛衣
Kendall would really appreciate it
肯德尔会很感谢的   -干嘛
if you took the sweater.  -What?
听好了  我男人很冷
-Hey, my partner is cold
他就想穿着他的外套  行吗
and he'd like to keep his fucking coat on, okay?
而且  他正在竞选下一届
And he's running to be the next President
美利坚合众国的总统
of the United States of America
所以  或许  你他妈最好对他放尊敬点
so maybe you should show him some fucking respect, okay?
真他妈阴魂不散
She would not fuck off.
是啊  真是的
Yeah, she did.
你好  我杀了个人才拿到的
Hi, I had to kill a man for it,
壮汉起开  让我进去
but step aside, hombre, let me in.
抱歉  先生  我真做不到   他说你不能进去
I'm sorry, sir. I really can't. He said you're not coming in
我知道  他开玩笑呢  他可是我哥啊
-Yeah. He was joking. That's my brother, okay?
你网上都能查到不是..   -先生
You can Google it. ..  Sir,
你用手碰我吗
Wow, are you touching me?
这人在猥亵宾客
This man is groping the guests.
你没得到我的允许
You do not have my permission.
我不允许你碰我
You do not have my permission to touch me.
你在这啊  他妈的躲我呢
Hey. There you are, fucking hiding from me.
像个人型虚拟专网一样
Like a human VPN.
你还好吗   -我挺好的
-How you doing? -I'm all right.
我只是.. 你还是自己脑补吧
I'm just... you know you can fill in the blanks.
我懂  操蛋的人生  对吧
No, I hear you. It's fucking life, right?
真他妈累死人了
It's fucking exhausting.
我就想享用个女人的性器官  然后走人  懂吧
I just wanna find a good pussy and get out, you know.
任务  支线任务   -我明白 兄弟
Mission, side mission. I hear you, man.
我他妈最爱女人的性器官了 你看见我妈的没
I fucking love pussy.   -You see my mom's?
看到了
-Yeah.
你见过我妈的吗
You seen my mom's?
行   -不...不怎么好
-Yeah. -It's not... it's not great.
是啊  不太好  我是不会碰的
No, sure. I mean, not touching that one.
有个问题
Question.
我老爸今早脾气有点大
My old man got a little bit grumpy this morning
但你并不是想羞辱他吧
but you weren't trying to humiliate him, right?
因为  所有人都说  真的  所有人都在说
I mean, everyone says, I mean, fucking everyone says
我们是最后一个大型老牌内容库
last big legacy content library
而你们  是最后一个超级流媒体平台
last fucking super app streaming platform.
我们般配得不得了
We fit, obviously, right?
大家都这么说   -是啊
-People say we fit. -Yeah.
那我确实也有一个问题
Well, I guess I do have one question though.
行  放马过来吧
Yeah, hit me up.
你爸什么时候死
When will your father die?
我爸... 我爸什么时候死
When will... when will my father die?
对
Yeah.
我无意冒犯  但...
Like, I don't wanna be rude,
他健康状况怎么样
but what kind of shape is he in?
是一年之内就要不行了  还是能撑过五年
We're talking less than a year or it's more like five years?
因为如果还能活五年  那..
'Cause if it's five, that's...
那就有点久
it's a long time.
快一点不是更好吗
It would be better sooner, wouldn't it? -Right?
不不不  我懂... 我们在这可以说笑
-No... I know, like  we're laughing here,
但那也是我爸  所以..
but, you know, that is my dad, so, you know...
行  好   -宽容点吧 老板
-Right. Yeah. -...go easy there, chief!
不..我能看出  你觉得这有点奇怪
No, I... I can tell that it's a bit weird for you.
没事
That's okay.
只是...我不喜欢感觉到有个人...
It's just I don't like the idea of a man
盘旋在我头上   -太他妈对了
hanging over me.  Oh, fuck yeah.
我能理解  谁他妈想要这样呢
No, I can understand. Who the fuck wants that? Yeah.
仿佛宗师一般  而他只是..只是他妈个屁
The guru guy who's fucking... fucking bullshit, you know?
懂了    -因为...
Okay.  'Cause
媒体不是我的领域
it's not my world, media.
好   -所以..
-Yeah. -So...
他的死能腾出空间
his death would clear space.
·无意冒犯   -没事  别见外  别见外
With due respect.  Yeah. No...
我知道  我们显然都非常..
I know.  I mean, like, we're all obviously
期待我爸一命鸣呼
hugely looking forward to my father dying
但.. 还有另外一种情况
but there's another shape to this.
如果你永远不用和他对话呢
How about you never ever have to speak to him?
你可以在奥斯汀
I mean, you work out of Austin,
伦敦 斯德哥尔摩 日内瓦 随便什么地方工作
London, Stockholm, Geneva, whatever.
完全独立的公司个体
Totally separate corporate identities
然后  我们把 Star Go 做掉   -对
and, StarGo, we burn, obviously.
好  非常好   -好
-Yes. Yes. Please. -Oh, yeah.
把那些代码毁了...
Like burn the codes
再给那些服务器洗个硫酸浴   -我们当然可以
and fucking acid bath those servers!  fucking we can do that.
我们可以一起做  来吧
We can do that together. Let's do it.
好   -完全可以  用你们的平台
Absolutely. I mean, GoJo full bore.
我们的内容库  我们的火力
I mean, our library, our firepower
我们的内容关系
our relationships for content.
都是好东西  你明白我意思吗
And like good shit, you know what I mean?
不是什么同性恋母亲或者轮椅小孩之类的破玩意
Like not fucking gay moms and wheelchair kids bullshit
是真正受欢迎的好内容
like, popular, actual good shit
如果你需要从日内瓦
and on the occasion that you need to send up
发一个烟雾信号的话
a fucking smoke signal from Geneva
那就由我来经手
then that goes through me.
你永远都不需要和我爸打交道
You won't ever, ever have to deal with him
行吧   -见他和他对话...什么都不需要
or see him, or talk to him, or hear... Nothing.
你知道 Star Go 纯他妈是个垃圾
And you know that StarGo truly, truly is a piece of shit, right?
真的烂透了 我知道
It's a piece of shit. I know.
我喜欢打开他们的程序
I like to open it just to see how long it takes
只为了看  加载登录页面要多久
for the landing page to load.
确实是烂透了  要不我们...
It is a piece of shit. Hey, why don't we...
不如我们直接往手机程序上撒泡尿吧
Why don't we just, like, take a big old piss on our app?
我在我的手机上打开程序
I'm going to open up the app on my phone
然后我们对准那个流媒体平台撒泡尿
and we can stream some piss on our little streaming platform.
听起来怎么样,   -太棒了
-How's that sound? -fuck yeah.
19...  20...
Nineteen, twenty,
21.. 22    -好了好了
twenty-one, twenty-two. Yeah...
我在别的男人面前尿不出来..
So I can't piss near other men
原因未知  但你请便
due to we don't know what reason, but please,
来吧   -请不要介意
go ahead.  -Don't mind if I do.
行  请便吧
-Yeah. Enjoy.
我知道 Go Jo 是你的心肝宝贝
So I know GoJo is your baby
我们不想对它进行任何干涉
and we do not wanna interfere with that at all.
你是天才   -我当然是
You're the genius.  Damn right I am.
所以  基于这点
Yup. So bearing that in mind
你能考虑见下我爸吗
would you consider meeting with my dad?
好啊
Yeah.
或许 对于把平台卖给我们也有兴趣
And you'd be interested in selling to us maybe?
如果你说的都是真的   那么..可以
Yeah, well, if all this is true, then... yeah.
周一如何   -周一完美
How's Monday? Monday is great.
如果我现在跟你握手
And if I were to shake your hand right now
我能告诉我爸  我刚为他买下了 Go Jo 吗
could I go tell my dad that I basically just bought GoJo for him?
不行
No.
但你可以告诉他  我愿意谈谈
But you can tell him I'm in the conversation.
太他妈棒了   没问题   -来吧接着
fucking A, I'll take it.  Okay. Take this.
成了
Will do.
我们很合拍吧
Are we amazing?
我有可能是全美最牛的生意人
I think I might be the best businessman in America.
你看看  还在加载呢
Hey, check this out. Still fucking loading.
你这垃圾   -垃圾
-You piece of shit. -Shit.
去你妈的
fuck you.
好了  如果你想套上安全带
Okay. If you wanna put on the harness
就先穿上燕尾服  然后站上踏板
you can tuxedo up and step up onto the footrest
我们会帮你穿戴好
and then we'll strap you in.
你有三十秒时间  绳索会带你上天
You'll have 30 seconds and the rig will fly you up
然后 就位
and into position
你会看到三二一 倒计时
you'll have a 3-2-1
然后就能看到绿火
and you'll see the green light, okay?
那是进场的倒数计时
That's the countdown to the intro.
你准备好 把比利·乔尔 钉上十字架了吗
You ready? You ready to crucify Billy Joel?
好的  好
Yeah.
我只是开玩笑  你会很棒的
I'm just kidding. You're gonna be great.
你记得他说的 绳索缠绕的事情吧
Remember the thing he said about the rig spiraling
所以  就不要乱动  那听起来很重要
so just, like, keep still, yeah? That sounded serious.
好了  安全带  然后拿上麦
Okay. Harness, then mic.
准备好了吗  你要换衣服吗
Ready to rock? You wanna get changed?
要不  这样
Yeah, you know what?
我有点不想表演了
I don't think I'm gonna do this.
你不表演了
-You don't wanna do it?
不...这太离谱了  不要了
-No, it's...it's bullshit. No.
因为你说过  如果你不震撼进场
Because you did say if you don't lean right in
就会显得很蠢
it could come across dumb.
而且你的演讲里也带有些讽刺
And your speech kind of tees it up with a kind of ironic
比如“这是我人生旅程的高潮
"This is the culmination of my life's journey.
为了救你们这些白痴而被钉死在十字架上..
To be crucified to save you morons and..."
我不干了  这...
I'm not doing it. It's...
这就像是  十五个硕士学位叠加起来那么离谱
it's like 15 layers overdetermined master's degree fucking hokum.
就..算了吧  这是干什么呢
Let's just... let's just pull it. I mean, what... What is it?
穿着燕尾服被钉在十字架上
It's dressed in a tuxedo nailed to a cross,
唱着比利·乔尔的“诚实"
singing Honesty by Billy Joel?
这他妈完全不合理
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
那小武当帮怎么办
What about the Tiny Wu Tang?
我操
fuck.
我没想好  我没...这样吧  我不想这样做了
I don't know. I don't... you know what? I don't think so.
不用了吗  好吧
No? Okay.
告诉他们  让他们搞定这一切吧
Tell 'em they've got it all ahead of them. Yeah.
真他妈的松了口气
That's a fucking relief.
你好
Oh, hey.
康福莉  派对情况如何   -挺好的
Hey, Comf.  -How's it going? -Hey. Good.
是吗   -是的  挺好的
-Yeah? -Yeah, it's good.
肯  让我试着联系  斯普林斯汀  来救场
Ken had me try to call Springsteen to rescue the vibe
然后他又改变主意了  现在我忙着给他找一个
and then that got countermanded and now I'm working on
喷气背包  让他能飞出  可收缩天花板
a jetpack for him to leave through the retractable ceiling
那个天花板得要48小时才能挪开  所以..
that takes 48 hours to move, so...
好吧
Okay. Yeah.
我是说  他的很多想法就是个笑话  但有的想法不是
Yeah, I mean a lot of the ideas are jokes but some aren't.
很奇怪  确实
Very weird. Yes, indeed.
怎么了
-What?
没事  我...没什么  就是..
-No, me... no, nothing.
就是个很蠢的想法  但之前
Yeah... it's stupid but earlier,
在我还没听说
before I heard
你在策划一个针对我的恶意营销的时候
you were gonna orchestrate a smear campaign against me
我...我其实想问你
I was actually gonna ask you
你想不想跟我出去喝一杯
if you wanted to grab a drink sometime.
这样啊
Oh, okay.
是的  但然后  肯德尔
Yeah, but then...Kendall,
你知道的  肯..肯德尔  他说.
you know, Kendall, he said...
他说什么了
He said what?
他就说  也许不要吧  划清界限  公私分明
He just said maybe not. Clean lines. Church and State.
错误的时间  错误的地点  但是...
Wrong time, wrong place. But
但也许
maybe
当...当你不在他手下工作了
when you're not working for him anymore
也没有在试着毁掉我的名声的时候
and trying to destroy my reputation and,
-还有诸如此类的... 你知道吗  我花了整整一周
and such... You know, I've spent a week researching
研究哪里可以买到80年代的午餐盒
where to get lunchboxes from the '80s
用来装点心的
to serve canapés from?
就是他小时候会带去学校的那种
Like the one he used to take to school
然后 他觉得他不想要午餐盒了
and then he decided that he didn't want lunchboxes
所以 现在这些巨人希曼的午餐盒 就在我的公寓堆着
and so now I have all these He-Man lunchboxes in my apartment
我得在易贝[二手售卖网站]上 把他们转手卖了
and I have to resell them on eBay
他办公室还要我提供发票
and his office wants receipts.
所以  如果你想要约我出去  那就约我吧
So if you wanna ask me out, then ask me out.
有空我们一起出去玩好吗   -好
Do you wanna go out sometime? Yes.
太好了
Great.
她...她真跳起来了
Wow. She's... she's really dancing there.
非常...非常自由
Very emancipated.
你知道她嗑什么了吗
Do you know what she's taken?
我觉得她什么都没嗑
I don't think she's taken anything.
我想 就是把内心的恶魔 释放出来吧
Just getting the demons out, I guess.
你找到我孩子送的礼物了吗
Hey, you found the gift from my kids?
我还没找到
I don't believe so.
没找到  好吧..这可不妙
No? Well, okay. That's not good.
让我们独处一会儿吧
Will you give us a moment, please?
显然 他们给我做了个东西  所以我得找到
They made me something, apparently so I gotta find it.
肯  礼物会出现的
Hey, Ken, it'll turn up.
如果我们不找的话  礼物是不会自己现身的
Well, it won't turn up if we don't look for it.
我当然知道  抱歉
-Well, I know that. -Sorry.
我只是随口一说
I'm sorry. I'm just saying.
到底他妈的在哪里
Where the fuck is it?
肯  停一停
Hey, Ken, take a break.
你想看看我送的礼物吗
You want my gift?
当然  我想看
Yeah. Yes, I would. Yes, I would love that.
是块手表   -好吧  谢谢
-It's a watch. -Okay. Wow. Yeah. Thanks.
谢谢你  内,   -我真的很不擅长送礼物
-I'm, like... -Thanks, Nay. ...really bad at presents
这..我喜欢  不错   -就..退货吧
-It... I like it, all right. -Just... just give it back.
不用  我喜欢这块表   -没事的
-No, I like it. -No, it's fine.
内  谢谢你这块表
Thanks, Nay. Is it...
给我看看这块表..
can I see?
是刻了字吗 还是.. -没有只是一块普通的手表
Is it...inscribed or... -No, it's just a stupid watch, okay?
我会送你点别的东西
I'll get you something else.
你想不想...我给你吹一次
Do you want a blow job?
不用了  就是.
No, it's just...
我不想犯浑   但我...我有手表了
I don't wanna be a dick but I have a watch
我有我的手表
you know, I have my watch.
这就是个差劲的礼物
-It's a shitty gift, okay?
我太...糟糕了   -不是的  内 听我说
I'm bad. -No, Nay, listen.
我就是想站在你的角度思考
Yeah, I'm just trying to get inside your head and figure out
你为什么要送我这个礼物
why you would give me this gift.
没事了
Yeah, it's fine.
挺好的   -肯
-It's fine. -Ken?
肯  行了
Hey, Ken, come on.
真的别这样  好吗  听我说.
Ken, come on, seriously, okay? Look...
我得找到那个礼物,   -别这样
I'm gonna look for that gift. Hey, stop.
肯  老天爷  冷静...别这样
Ken, Jesus. Hey, calm... Stop... stop.
冷静一下
Just chill.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没事的
It's okay.
太难过了
This is so pathetic.
我好希望 我现在...
I wish I was...
怎么了
What?
我好希望 我现在 在家
I wish I was home.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
格雷格  我挺好的  为什么你一直问我好不好
Yes, I'm okay, Greg. Why do you keep asking if I'm okay?
只是...我已经六个小时没看见你笑了
Well, just... I haven't seen you smile in, like, six hours.
格雷格  你不需要用笑容来表达开心
You don't have to smile to be happy, Greg.
我在享受  琢磨我自己
I'm enjoying very much thinking about myself
还有我各种技能和能力
and my own various skills and abilities.
要不 我们试试 这条美妙的隧道吧
-Shall we try the compliment tunnel?
当然   -可能会很美妙
-Sure. It could be nice.
你为什么这么高兴
Why are you so happy?
我吗   -对
-Me? -Yeah.
其实 因为我
Well, actually, because I...
我遇见了世界上最好的女孩儿
I have met the most wonderful girl in the world.
你们太棒了
You're just fantastic.
那是当然  太棒了
Yes, I am. Amazing. Amazing.
我的意思是  可能她跟我出去
I mean, it's possible she's only going out with me
只是出于  你懂的  怨恨和愤怒
due to, you know, rancor or pique.
你是如此充满恩典
-You're so full of grace.
什么  -我觉得他是说你充满恩典
-What's that?  I think he said you're full of grace.
这话好奇怪  你是在讽刺吗
That's a weird thing to say.  You being sarcastic?
他是在讽刺吗   -不  我觉得他的意思是...
He being sarcastic?  -No, I think it's...
充满恩...充满他妈的什么  你说什么
-He said fucking full of grace. Full of fucking what? What?
你刚才说了什么  -等等汤姆 汤.. 放轻松
What did you say?  Wait. Tom, easy.
他只是..你是在做你的工作  对吧
He's just... you're doing the job, right?
今晚他吸了点可卡因  所以我觉得他..
And he's had a little cocaine tonight, so I think he's...
兄弟 别说那点  别说
Dude, don't say that.
我是公众人物  也许有天 会参政的
I'm a public figure who could one day run for high office
或者引领一家财富五百强  别那样说
or lead a Fortune 500. Don't say that.
好吧  他是个很可爱的人
All right. He's a lovely guy.
你的工作做得很好
You're doing great work.
你太高兴了
You're so merry.
这个嘛  只是...
Well, yeah, it's just...
我不知道  我...我很兴奋  要去约会了  我喜欢她
I don't know. I'm excited about my date. I like her.
怎么说呢  真令人兴奋  -你是最棒的
-What can I say? It's exciting. -You're the best.
谢谢你   -滚开
-Thank you. -fuck off.
格雷格  你看上去比我开心多了
You seem much happier than me, Greg.
我想我感觉快乐吧  这并不是一块有限的馅饼
I feel happy. I guess... it's not a finite pie
我们都可以快乐   -当然
-we can both be happy. -Sure.
快乐的人  本应该是我  但现在是你
But it's supposed to be me that's happy and it's you.
怎么会这样
How did that happen?
我以错误的顺序  嗑了错误的药
I took the wrong drugs in the wrong order
我开心不起来
and I can't get happy.
你不能为了自由开心吗
Well, can't you just be happy you're free?
不能  因为你把它毁了
No, 'cause you've ruined it.
我怎么毁的   -我不知道  反正是你
-How have I ruined it? -I don't know. You just have.
她来了   -你好
-Hey, there she is.
你干嘛呢  发生了什么
-Hey. What are you up to?  What's going on?
我听说你在谈 你找到马特森了吗
I heard you were speaking.  -Did you get to Matsson?
你还好吗
-Are you okay?
观众说你有些崩溃
On-lookers reported you having some kind of breakdown.
他们还怕你咬舌自尽
People were anxious that you maybe swallowed your tongue.
对  我当时在跳舞
Yeah, I was dancing.
我怎么听说  是你好像迫切需要帮助
I heard it looked like a cry for help.
糖梅跛子[原为仙子]之舞
The Dance of the Sugar Plum Failure.
滚蛋  你和他搭上话没    -那当然
fuck you. You spoke to him? -Yup.
然后呢  -我能不说吗
-And? Do you mind if I don't say?
你...快讲
Okay... Okay, come on.
好吧  小西  别担心  我能处理好
All right. Don't worry about it, Shivvy. I'll handle it.
你去劲舞吧
You can go cut a rug.
罗曼  认真点  快说   -我很认真啊
Rome, seriously, come on. I am being serious.
我会去问爸  看他让不让你加入
I will talk to Dad and see if he wants to loop you in.
他确实总这么想
He often does like to loop you in.
罗曼  你最好赶快告诉我
Rome, just... just fucking tell me.
这事很重要  我可能还需要使些手段
This is important and I might need to finesse.
你需要使些手段吗   -是的
-Oh, you need to finesse? -Yeah.
谢谢您  您真善良
Thank you. That's kind.
你怎么对已经办完的事使手段
How would you finesse something that's done?
怎么  你想搅黄吗
What? By ruining it?
不  确保你不会...事实是
-No, by making sure you don't... -The thing is
卢卡斯和我似乎很有默契
that Lukas and I have, like, a thing
而你不一定合得来
and I don't see how you fit in.
你知道吗  你要是想跟人炫耀
You know what? If you wanna show off to somebody
就找个 会把你的话放在心上的人吧
maybe do it to someone who gives a shit.
今天你过得很糟  我知道
You're having a very bad day. I know that.
我听说了
What, with hearing
你还得继续跟那个人肉衣橱继续住在一起
that you have to continue to share your apartment with the old meat wardrobe
但是你应该知道
but, you know,
冷静点吧  行吗
try to keep your wig on, yeah?
我才是那个处于正常男女关系里的人,   -可不是嘛
I'm the one in a functioning relationship. Sure you are.
我看到了 你知道吗  我看见你喝了爸的香槟
I saw you, you know.  I saw you sipping Dad's champagne
跟吸柠檬一样
looking like you were sucking a lemon.
我工作日不喝酒.
I don't drink on work days
你工作日不喝酒   -...因为我自律
-You don't drink on work days. -because I have self-control.
好  原来是这样
Okay. That's what that is.
我还以为
Okay. I thought
你在想  他被关起来以后
maybe you were thinking about all the dick
能坐上谁的老二   -我了个操啊
you were gonna ride when he was inside?  Oh, my fucking God.
你知道吗
You know what?
没人像你一样喜欢谈论我和男人做爱的事
No one likes talking about me fucking guys as much as you do.
你知道吗
Do you know that?
为什么呢  因为你是性功能障碍的首席运营官吗
Why is that?  Is that because you're the COO who can't fuck?
你曾认为汤姆会坐牢吗
Did you think Tom was going to jail?
会吗 会吗   -不  他不坐牢我很开心
-Did you? Did you? Did you?  -No, I'm happy he's not going... -to jail.
可不是嘛  你看起来真开心
-Oh, I'm sure you are. You look really happy.
但你曾认为会  是吗  也许吗
Did you think he was though? Maybe?
他还是有可能会坐牢的吧
He... there was a chance he was going to jail?
或者老爸去坐牢
Maybe Dad was gonna go to jail?
操  搞不好我也会坐牢
fuck. Maybe I was gonna go to jail.
因为  肯德尔疯了
And because Kendall's...
所以  一切都围着你转
that it was all about you.
你以为今晚是女士之夜
You thought it was ladies' night
还放着你的主题曲  但是猜猜怎么着
and they were playing your song.  But guess what,
你大错特错了
you're wrong.
所有的男人都去了男人帮
All the men got together in man club
然后我们决定说  小甜心  一切都好呢...
and we decided, sweetheart, everything's fine, so just...
我们能行的,   -他只是在利用你
-We got it. -You know he is......using you
做他的传话小弟  但  像往常一样..
as a messenger boy.  But, as usual,
..你还傻得看不清
you're too fucking dumb to see it.
这很难  我理解  对你来说极其难
It's difficult. I get it. It's very difficult for you
要为老爸跳舞  可是你跳得太烂了
to have to do the dance for Dad because you just suck at dancing.
你就是王八蛋  你知道吗
You're a piece of shit, you know that?
结果爸超爱看我给他跳舞
It turns out he loves it when I do the Daddy dance
我猜这是因为他爱我
but I guess that's because he loves me.
他特别喜欢操我  他只是不再想要操你了
He loves fucking me, and he just doesn't wanna fuck you anymore.
你到底在说些什么  你太恶心了
What are you even talking about? You're so gross.
爸爸不爱他的黄毛丫头了
Well, Daddy doesn't love his little carrot top
就算她给爸爸跳舞
even when she does her little Daddy dance.
爸爸舞 爸爸舞   -我他妈恨死你了  兄弟
Dad-daddy, dad-daddy dance.  -I fucking hate you, you know?
靠  看谁来了  大寿星
-Oh, shit. Look at this. It's birthday boy.
生日快乐啊   -够了  好吗
Hey, happy birthday, man.  -Enough, yeah?
好的  抱歉  晚安啊
-Oh, okay. Yeah. Sorry. Good night.
你们两个都不该来
Neither of you should be in here.
天啊  你是对的  来人啊  叫警察
Oh, my God, you're right. Someone call the cops!
有人闯入自慰馆了
Intruders have breached the Masturbatorium!
你俩满嘴放炮
You're both full of shit.
来这儿背着我搞鬼
And you came here to fuck me behind my back.
俩恶心的食尸鬼
And you're ghouls and you're disgusting.
抱歉哦  -能把他们赶出去吗
Sorry. Whoops. Can we get them out?
请出去吗   -能把他们赶出去吗
-Oh, get them out? -Can we get them out, please.
这有点迟了
It's a little late for that,
伙计  我跟马特森谈过了
buddy.  I already spoke to Matsson
顺便说一句  他恨死你了  总是在嘲讽你
who hates you, by the way, and laughs at you constantly.
别说了
-Just stop.
怎么  要对寿星好一点吗
-Oh, what?  Go easy on birthday boy?
你们来这儿  根本不是来看我的吧
Did you come here to see me at all?
不是吧  是吗  小西
You didn't, did you, Shiv?
是这样的  我们最近相处得不是很好
Well, look, we haven't been getting along that great lately
所以  你觉得呢  很意外吗
so what do you think? Surprised?
收购 Go Jo 是我想到的
GoJo was my idea.
你们刺窃了我的想法   “你们刺窃了我的想法
-You stole my idea. -"You stole my idea."
你他妈几岁啊  六岁吗
What are you, fucking six?
你输了  这没什么大不了
Dude, you lost. No big deal.
没必要哭泣  你只是输了而已
No need to cry about it. You lost.
你喜欢监视别人吗  小西  监视我女儿
You like the spying, Shiv? On my daughter,
你侄女  你喜欢吗
on your niece? You like that?
够了  肯  别再吸毒了,   -这算什么事
Okay. Lay off the drugs, Ken. Not a fucking big deal.
谁在乎呢   -我们确实在监视吗
Who gives a shit? -We are spying?
是的..拜托  当然啊
-Yes, of... oh, come on. Of course we are.
这是场派对游戏  他这不是在找爸的麻烦
It's a fucking party game.   He's in Dad's shit,
听以咱们也找他麻烦   大家都在找他麻烦
so we're up in his   everybody's in his shit.
别装得一脸无辜   -不  这太不堪了
Don't act like you're fucking clean. Okay. That is disgusting.
不堪吗  你现在跟他站一边了吗  叛徒
It's disgusting? What, you're siding with him now? Traitor?
我只是说  要有底线  哥
I'm just saying there's a line, bro.
竟然监视苏菲和艾弗森
fucking Sophie and Iverson?
他们还是孩子
They're kids.
现在又有底线了吗  他都没有底线
There's a fucking line now? No line for him,
你也没有   我就得有吗
no line for you.  But there's a line for me?
你俩就是自大的傻逼
You're a bunch of stuck up cunts
就是看不得我赢
who can't fucking bear to see me win.
就是这样  明摆着
-That's it. That's all this is.
你都不算真正的人
You're not a real person.
你知道吗  你不是真正的人
You know that? You're not a real person.
你算不上人
You're not real.
来  要不你打我一拳
Come on. Why don't you hit me maybe?
咱们走吧   -来啊  假耶稣
-Come on. -Come on, shitty Jesus.
你心里想打我  来啊  动手啊
You know you want to, just fucking hit me. Do it.
还"我不是真正的人“去你妈的
"I'm not a real person." fuck you.
好吧  我错了  我错了
All right. I'm sorry.
好好过生日  好吗  大臭脸
Have a good birthday, okay, fuckface?
这怎么回事   -不好  操了
-Hey, what is this? -Oh, shit! Oh, fuck,
你还好吗  生日快乐啊
are you okay?   -Happy birthday.
大家冷静点  好吗
-Everybody just take it easy, okay?
把外套脱了
Take your coat off.
你他妈把外套脱了   -够了够了
-Take your fucking coat off. -That's enough.
你他妈把外套脱了
Take your fucking coat off!
跟他妈八岁孩子一样
He's such a fucking hater.
你真是个混蛋
You're an asshole.
太有趣了  太有趣了
It's funny. It's funny.
你待会儿会笑出来的   -我们..走..
You're gonna laugh at it later.
你半夜会醒来...
You're gonna wake up in the middle of the night
我们走吧   -想着刚才真搞笑
and be like, "That was funny."
敬寿星
To the birthday boy.
你想去别的地方吗
Hey, you wanna go someplace else?
比如出城  就现在
Like out out now?
不了  宝贝
No thanks, honey.
我可能得出去一下
I might be up for a while.
喂  爸  我搞定他了
Hey, Dad. I nailed him.
我是你唯一需要的孩子了
I am the only child you'll ever need.
你可以把其他人宰了  爱你哦
You can kill the others. Love you.
你们滚吧  我走路回家
Hey, you can piss off. I'm gonna walk home.
还好吗
Hey.
聚会结束了吧
I think the party's over, yeah?
对  就是个聚会而已
Yeah. Just the party.
随它去吧  进屋吧
Let it fizzle.  Come.